Preliminary Guide to the Gelman Library, Slavic, East European, and Asian Reading Room records, 1962-1995 RG0132
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Office files, 1962-1995; RG0132 Series 2; 36 Linear feet
  - East Asia and Problems of Detente, 07/09/1978-07/13/1978 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Informal Notes, Supplementary Material
  - East Asia and Problems of Detente, 07/09/1978-07/13/1978 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Program, Participants, Guest list
  - East Asia and Problems of Detente, 07/09/1978-07/13/1978 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Participant Papers (Soviet)
  - East Asia and Problems of Detente, 07/09/1978-07/13/1978 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Final Report
  - Marxism in the Contemporary West, 04/1979 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Manuscript
  - Soviet and Chinese Policy in Africa, 03/14/1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Program, Participants
  - Eastern Europe in the 1980s [1/2], 04/04/1980-04/05/1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Conference, Papers
  - Eastern Europe in the 1980s [2/2], 04/04/1980-04/05/1980 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Security Problems in East Asia, 11/21/1980-11/22/1980 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Security Problems in East Asia, 11/21/1980-11/22/1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Praeger Publisher Correspondence
  - Security Problems in East Asia, 11/21/1980-11/22/1980 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Revised Manuscripts from Conference
  - Security Problems in East Asia, 11/21/1980-11/22/1980 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Praeger Manuscript
  - Security Problems in East Asia, 11/21/1980-11/22/1980 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Peace and Security in Asia, 05/11/1981-05/14/1981 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Correspondence, Program, Participants
  - Peace and Security in Asia, 05/11/1981-05/14/1981 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Notes
  - Peace and Security in Asia, 05/11/1981-05/14/1981 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Peace and Security in Asia, 05/11/1981-05/14/1981 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Changes in the Status of Women in Eastern Europe, 12/04/1981-12/06/1981 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Changes in the Status of Women in Eastern Europe, 12/04/1981-12/06/1981 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Changes in the Status of Women in Eastern Europe, 12/04/1981-12/06/1981 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Changes in the Status of Women in Eastern Europe, 12/04/1981-12/06/1981 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Changes in the Status of Women in Eastern Europe, 12/04/1981-12/06/1981 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Changes in the Status of Women in Eastern Europe, 12/04/1981-12/06/1981 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Role of the State in Development and Change in China, 12/14/1981-12/15/1981 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Program, Plans, Participants
  - Role of the State in Development and Change in China, 12/14/1981-12/15/1981 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Role of the State in Development and Change in China [1/4], 12/14/1981-12/15/1981 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Role of the State in Development and Change in China [2/4], 12/14/1981-12/15/1981 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Role of the State in Development and Change in China [3/4], 12/14/1981-12/15/1981 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Role of the State in Development and Change in China [4/4], 12/14/1981-12/15/1981 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Korean Economic Miracle, 03/14/1983 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Korea and Northeast Asia in the 1980s [1/2], 03/27/1983-03/30/1983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Korea and Northeast Asia in the 1980s [2/2], 03/27/1983-03/30/1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Korea and Northeast Asia in the 1980s, 03/27/1983-03/30/1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Third Joint Conference on Asia [1/3], 05/11/1983-05/14/1983 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Proceedings
  - Third Joint Conference on Asia [2/3], 05/11/1983-05/14/1983 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Third Joint Conference on Asia [3/3], 05/11/1983-05/14/1983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Third Joint Conference on Asia, 05/11/1983-05/14/1983 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Third Joint Conference on Asia, 05/11/1983-05/14/1983 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 12th Sino-American Conference on Mainland China [1/6], 06/09/1983-06/12/1983 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 12th Sino-American Conference on Mainland China [2/6], 06/09/1983-06/12/1983 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 12th Sino-American Conference on Mainland China [3/6], 06/09/1983-06/12/1983 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 12th Sino-American Conference on Mainland China [4/6], 06/09/1983-06/12/1983 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 12th Sino-American Conference on Mainland China [5/6], 06/09/1983-06/12/1983 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 12th Sino-American Conference on Mainland China [6/6], 06/09/1983-06/12/1983 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 12th Sino-American Conference on Mainland China, 06/09/1983-06/12/1983 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 12th Sino-American Conference on Mainland China, 06/09/1983-06/12/1983 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Keynote Address, Program, Participants
  - 12th Sino-American Conference on Mainland China, 06/09/1983-06/12/1983 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Correspondence with Taiwan
  - 12th Sino-American Conference on Mainland China, 06/09/1983-06/12/1983 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Co-sponsor Correspondence
  - Northeast Asia in World Politics, 05/14/1984-05/16/1984 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Northeast Asia in World Politics, 05/14/1984-05/16/1984 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Objectives and Problems of International Broadcasting, 10/20/1984 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Reciprocity and Superpower Relations, 12/07/1984 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Peace and Security in Asia, 12/07/1984 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Views, Administrative Report
  - Peace and Security in Asia, 12/07/1984 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Plans, Correspondence
  - Search for Political Settlement in Asia [1/2], 05/13/1985-05/15/1985 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Search for Political Settlement in Asia [2/2], 05/13/1985-05/15/1985 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Search for Political Settlement in Asia, 05/13/1985-05/15/1985 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Search for Political Settlement in Asia, 05/13/1985-05/15/1985 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    Japanese Language Press Articles
  - Search for Political Settlement in Asia, 05/13/1985-05/15/1985 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    English Language Press Articles (Japanese Press)
  - Peace and Security in Asia, 06/25/1985-06/28/1985 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - MAR/AAS Annual Meeting, 10/25/1985-10/27/1985 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Program, Arrangements
  - U.S. Japan Economic Agenda, 01/17/1986-01/18/1986 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    Newsletters, Roundtable, Program
  - Occasional Papers/More Continuity that Change, 02/1986 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Europe in Transition, 02/03/1986 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    Participants, Questions
  - Nuclear Technology Transfer to Asia, 02/27/1986-02/28/1986 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    Westview Press Correspondence
  - Nuclear Technology Transfer to Asia, 02/27/1986-02/28/1986 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Nuclear Technology Transfer to Asia, 02/27/1986-02/28/1986 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - U.S. Japan Economic Agenda, 04/23/1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Speech Allen Wallis
  - U.S. Japan Economic Agenda, 04/23/1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Briefing
  - Korean Nationalism and U.S. Foreign Policy, 05/15/1986 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Speech Lee Min Woo
  - International Conference on Peace and Security in Asia, 05/22/1986-05/24/1986 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Program Participants
  - International Conference on Peace and Security in Asia, 05/22/1986-05/24/1986 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Problems of Peace and Security in Asia, 05/29/1986-05/31/1986 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Japan Economic Agenda, 06/02/1986 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Speech Gaston Sigur
  - Sino American Conference on Mainland China, 06/08/1986-06/14/1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Sino American Conference on Mainland China [1/2], 06/08/1986-06/14/1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Sino American Conference on Mainland China [2/2], 06/08/1986-06/14/1986 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Japan Economic Agenda, 06/16/1986 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Speech Paula Stern
  - International Society for the Systems Sciences/ILHAE Foundation, Seoul Korea, 11/03/1986-11/04/1986 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - International Society for the Systems Sciences/ILHAE Foundation, Seoul Korea, 11/03/1986-11/04/1986 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Project Development
  - Korea U.S. Conference on Northeast Asian Security, 12/01/1986-12/03/1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Korea U.S. Conference on Northeast Asian Security, 12/01/1986-12/03/1986 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Japan Economic Agenda, 04/06/1987 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Speech Harold Brown
  - Problems of Peace and Security in Asia [1/2], 05/28/1987-05/30/1987 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Problems of Peace and Security in Asia [2/2], 05/28/1987-05/30/1987 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Problems of Peace and Security in Asia, 05/28/1987-05/30/1987 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    Newspaper Articles
  - Problems of Peace and Security in Asia, 05/28/1987-05/30/1987 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Sino-American Conference on Asian Pacific Affairs [1/2], 06/15/1987-06/17/1987 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Sino-American Conference on Asian Pacific Affairs [2/2], 06/15/1987-06/17/1987 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Sino-American Conference on Asian Pacific Affairs, 06/15/1987-06/17/1987 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    Schedule Program
  - Problems of Peace and Security in Asia, 09/24/1987-09/26/1987 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    Participants Itineraries
  - Problems of Peace and Security in Asia, 09/24/1987-09/26/1987 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    International Research and Exchange Board Financial Information
  - Problems of Peace and Security in Asia, 09/24/1987-09/26/1987 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    International Research and Exchange Board Correspondence and Conference Report
  - Problems of Peace and Security in Asia, 09/24/1987-09/26/1987 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    Moscow Correspondence
  - Problems of Peace and Security in Asia, 09/24/1987-09/26/1987 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    Papers American
  - Problems of Peace and Security in Asia, 09/24/1987-09/26/1987 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    Papers Soviet
  - Global Information Revolution and East West Relations, 10/15/1987 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    Programs
  - American Association of Chinese Studies, 10/23/1987-10/25/1987 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    Program
  - American Association of Chinese Studies, 10/23/1987-10/25/1987 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    Arrangements Correspondence
  - American Association of Chinese Studies, 10/23/1987-10/25/1987 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    Arrangements Hotel Information
  - American Association of Chinese Studies, 10/23/1987-10/25/1987 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Peace Security and Economic Cooperation in the Asian Pacific, 04/25/1988-04/27/1988 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Peace Security and Economic Cooperation in the Asian Pacific, 04/25/1988-04/27/1988 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    Papers Chinese
  - Peace Security and Economic Cooperation in the Asian Pacific, 04/25/1988-04/27/1988 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Peace Security and Economic Cooperation in the Asian Pacific, 04/25/1988-04/27/1988 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Peace Security and Economic Cooperation in the Asian Pacific, 04/25/1988-04/27/1988 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Balkan Project: Background and Hoffman, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Memos
  - Balkan Conference: International Society for the Systems Sciences/GWU/United States Information Agency, 1987-1990 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Balkan Project: United States Information Agency AU17630, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    CVs Authors and Comments
  - Balkan Conference: International Society for the Systems Sciences, GWU, and United States Information Agency, 1987-1990 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Balkan Project, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    United States Information Agency Grant Guidelines
  - Balkan Conference, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Authors
  - Balkan Project, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Author Outlines
  - Balkan Conference [1/2], 1988 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Balkan Conference [2/2], 1988 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Balkan Project, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Letters to Publishers
  - Balkan Project Preliminary Meeting, 04/1988 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Summaries of Proceedings
  - Problems of Peace and Security Asia/Pac, 05/19/1988-05/21/1988 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Participants Program
  - Problems of Peace and Security Asia/Pac, 05/19/1988-05/21/1988 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Invitations
  - Problems of Peace and Security Asia/Pac, 05/19/1988-05/21/1988 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Miscellaneous
  - International Society for the Systems Sciences/Korean Association of Communist Studies Seoul Korea [1/2], 07/1988 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - International Society for the Systems Sciences/Korean Association of Communist Studies Seoul Korea [2/2], 07/1988 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - International Society for the Systems Sciences/Korean Association of Communist Studies Seoul Korea, 07/1988 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Foreign and Domestic Developments in NE Asia, 09/15/1988-09/17/1988 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Foreign and Domestic Developments in NE Asia, 09/15/1988-09/17/1988 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Program Participants Invitations
  - International Studies Association Conference, 11/1988 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    Conference Materials
  - International Society for the Systems Sciences/ACAPA, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    Seminars
  - International Society for the Systems Sciences/ACAPA Workshop: Changing Patterns in East West Relations [1/2], 04/02/1990 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - International Society for the Systems Sciences/ACAPA Workshop: Changing Patterns in East West Relations [2/2], 04/02/1990 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - International Society for the Systems Sciences/ACAPA Workshop: Changing Patterns in East West Relations, 04/02/1990 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    Program, Corrected Invitation
  - Blaga Dimitrova Visit, 04/1990 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Donations
  - Japan - U.S. Friendship Commission, 05/1990 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    Workshop Papers
  - Japan - U.S. Friendship Commission, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Soviet Economy Journal "R" Fund, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    Establishment and Abolition
  - Balkan Project Munich Program, 01/1989 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    Commentators Comments Papers
  - Balkan Project, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    Paul Shoup Editor
  - Multilateral Conference International Society for the Systems Sciences/Yomiuri Shimbun Tokyo Japan, 05/1989 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    American and Non-English Papers
  - Multilateral Conference International Society for the Systems Sciences/Yomiuri Shimbun Tokyo Japan, 05/1989 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    Non-American Participants Papers in English
  - Multilateral Conference International Society for the Systems Sciences/Yomiuri Shimbun Tokyo Japan, 05/1989 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    Programs, Participants
  - North Korean Conference, 04/1989 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    Canceled 03/1989
  - Conference on Moscow and Northern European Security, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Su Shao Zhi Visit, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Bilateral Conference, Beijing, 06/1989 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    Postponed, Papers
  - Bilateral Conference, 06/01/1989-06/03/1989 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    Postponed, Correspondence
  - Conference on Mainland China and Taiwan, 09/15/1989-09/16/1989 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Conference on Mainland China and Taiwan, 09/15/1989-09/16/1989 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    Correspondence and Budget
  - Mainland China and Taiwan: Comparisons and Interactions, 09/15/1989-09/16/1989 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Estonian Conference, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    Grant Application
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    Rejected 1989
  - Eastern Europe Conference, 05/1990 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Multilateral Conference International Society for the Systems Sciences/Yomiuri Shimbun, 05/17/1990-05/19/1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Japanese and American Papers
  - Multilateral Conference International Society for the Systems Sciences/Yomiuri Shimbun, 05/17/1990-05/19/1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Papers (except Japanese and American)
  - Multilateral Conference, 05/17/1990-05/19/1990 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Multilateral Conference, 05/17/1990-05/19/1990 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Bilateral Conference, 06/05/1990-06/07/1990 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Korean Association of Communist Studies [1/3], 06/18/1990-06/19/1990 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Korean Association of Communist Studies [2/3], 06/18/1990-06/19/1990 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Korean Association of Communist Studies, 06/18/1990-06/19/1990 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Korean Association of Communist Studies [3/3], 06/18/1990-06/19/1990 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - North Korean Visit, 09/1990 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Canceled
  - Institute of Far Eastern Studies Visit, 09/1990 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research:Millar, The Changing Soviet Citizen, contract, 10/19/1990 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    804-13, final report
  - Background Information for Millar Welcome Speech, 11/1990 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Korean Political Seminar, 12/1990 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Japan U.S. Friendship Commission, 12/1990 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Workshop Papers Study Project
  - Exchange Program Charles University: Prague, Czechoslovakia, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Department of Education: Title VI, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Student Account information
  - Department of Education: Title VI, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    Correspondence, Naomi Poling, deceased 04/1996
  - Department of Education: Title VI, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Subcontract, Georgetown University
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research, 06/1990-06/1991 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    AU 19630, correspondence
  - Ford Foundation, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Institute of Far Eastern Studies, 01/1991 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - United States Information Agency Proposal, 02/1991 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Millar/Trachtenberg Moscow Trip, 05/1991 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - China Institute of Contemporary International Relations Conference, 05/06/1991-05/08/1991 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    program, participants
  - China Institute of Contemporary International Relations Conference, 05/06/1991-05/08/1991 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    Chinese papers
  - China Institute of Contemporary International Relations Conference, 05/06/1991-05/08/1991 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    American papers
  - Multilateral Conference Yomiuri Shimbun [1/2], 05/27/1991-05/29/1991 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Multilateral Conference Yomiuri Shimbun [2/2], 05/27/1991-05/29/1991 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Multilateral Conference Yomiuri Shimbun, 05/27/1991-05/29/1991 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research: Social Stratification, General Social Survey of the European USSR, 05/1991 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    Swafford, AU19632, Codebook
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research: Social Stratification, General Social Survey of the European USSR, 05/1991 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    Swafford, AU19632, Questionnaire, Russian
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research: Social Stratification, General Social Survey of the European USSR, 05/1991 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    Swafford, AU19632, Questionnaire, English
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research: Social Stratification, General Social Survey of the European USSR, 05/1991 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    Swafford, AU19632, Survey Procedures,
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    Swafford, AU19632, correspondence
  - Institute of Economics, Moscow: Conference in Washington, 10/1991 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - International Society for the Systems Sciences/SOTOBO/Sigur Center: The Shattered Soviet Economy and its Foreign Relations with the U.S. and Japan, 11/21/1991 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - George Mason University, Grand Hotel, 03/1992 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - International Institute: George Mason University, 03/1992 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Multilateral Conference Yomiuri Shimbun, 05/28/1992-05/30/1992 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Multilateral Conference Yomiuri Shimbun, 05/28/1992-05/30/1992 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    Participants, Program, Welcome
  - Multilateral Conference Yomiuri Shimbun, 05/28/1992-05/30/1992 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    Sponsored Research
  - Multilateral Conference Yomiuri Shimbun, 05/28/1992-05/30/1992 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    Correspondence, Final Report
  - Multilateral Conference Yomiuri Shimbun, 05/28/1992-05/30/1992 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - European Community Studies Association conference: Background, undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
    planned for 05/1992, cancelled
  - International Society for the Systems Sciences/Chinese Academy of Sciences: Reform Change Transformation, 06/1992 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Chinese Academy of Social Sciences, 06/1992 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    Program, Participants, Papers
  - Institute for European, Russian, and Eurasian Studies/CIA conference on Survey Research, 9/1992 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - U.S. Institute of Peace/Lewis, 07/01/1992-06/30/1993 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - United States Information Agency, AU77601: Charles University Exchange Program, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - United States Information Agency, AU77601: Charles University Exchange Program, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    welcome letter
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research, 1992-1995 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Swafford, AU19634
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research: General Social Survey of the Russian Federation, 12/1992 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research: General Social Survey of Kazakhstan, Kyrgyzstan and Uzbekistan, 12/1992 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research: General Social Survey of the Russian Federation and Central Asia, 12/1992 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Swafford, AU19632, Survey Procedures
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research: General Social Survey of the Russian Federation and Central Asia, 12/1992 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research: General Social Survey of the Russian Federation and Central Asia, 12/1992 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - IERES Conference with CIA: Prospects for Democracy in Russia, 12/02/1993-12/03/1993 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    summary by James R.Millar
  - IERES Conference with CIA: Prospects for Democracy in Russia, 12/02/1993-12/03/1993 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    program, participants, budget development
  - IERES Conference with CIA: Prospects for Democracy in Russia, 12/02/1993-12/03/1993 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    correspondence with CIA
  - IERES/ROTOBO Conference: Russia, Japan, and the Japan Sea Rim, 11/1993 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    program, participants, papers
  - IERES/Sigur Center: Conference on Northeast Asia and Russia, 03/1994 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Ed McCord's Seminar on War in Modern China [1/2], 02/10/1995-02/11/1995 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    papers
  - Ed McCord's Seminar on War in Modern China [2/2], 02/10/1995-02/11/1995 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Ed McCord's Seminar on War in Modern China, 02/10/1995-02/11/1995 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    program, participant addresses
  - IERES/ROTOBO (Tokyo): Conference, Washington, 09/21/1995-09/22/1995 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    correspondence with ROTOBO
  - IERES/ROTOBO (Tokyo): Conference, Washington, 09/21/1995-09/22/1995 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    program, participants, biographies
  - IERES/ROTOBO (Tokyo): Conference, Washington, 09/21/1995-09/22/1995 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - National Defense Education Act, Title VI: Fellowship application, 10/15/1965 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - National Defense Education Act, Title VI: Intensive Summer Program in Chinese Language and Area Studies, 06/13/1966-08/26/1966 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - National Defense Education Act, Title VI: Fellowship application, 10/1966 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    awarded 12/02/1966, 3 in East Asian, For years 1967-1968
  - National Defense Education Act, Title VI: Fellowships, Chinese program, 10/1967 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    For years 1968-1969
  - National Defense Education Act, Title VI: Fellowships, Chinese and Russian programs, 10/1968 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    For 1969-1968
  - National Defense Education Act, Title VI: National Defense Education Act Center continuation, 10/1969 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    For years 1970-1971